A Guide to the Charles F. Gillette, Papers, ca. 1880-1985 (bulk 1918-1969)
Library of Virginia
- Client Correspondence and Card File, 1921-1968.
  In addition to the container listing found in this finding aid, the research can also search for client correspondence on the Gillette Drawings and Correspondence Database. While this searchable database was primarily created for the extensive list of Gillette's project drawings, it does include complete information on the client correspondence files. The card files are not included in this database. Researchers interested in finding correspondence can search under Gillette Account Number, Client Control Number, and Client Name. The page also includes a drop-down list of clients organized alphabetically by the last name of the client or the business name. General searches, such as a Client Name search of "Jones," returns a list of results containing links that will take the researcher to the full listing for that client name or client control number. As previously stated, correspondence does not survive for all projects. It is important to note that not all of Gillette's materials survive and a search may yield no results.
  - A General, 1942-1965 (Box 4, Folder 1)
    Gillette account number: None
  - Abingdon Church, - CCN 1 1955-1956 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Addison, Mrs.Edward- CCN 2 1945-1946 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Adkins, M. C.- CCN 3 1962-1965 (Box 4, Folder 4)
    Gillette account number: 2343
  - Albemarle Paper Company, - CCN 4 1957-1968 (Box 4, Folder 5)
    Gillette account number: 2176
  - Alexandria Garden Club, - CCN 5 1947 (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Alford, Mrs.D. L., Jr.- CCN 6 1950-1951 (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Altavista, Town of, - CCN 7 1950 (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - American Legion, - CCN 8 1944-1945 (Box 4, Folder 9)
    Gillette account number: 287
  - American Oil Company, - CCN 9 1955-1957 (Box 4, Folder 10)
    Gillette account number: 2091
  - Anderson, Mrs.Clifford Edward- CCN 10 1942-1963 (Box 4, Folder 11)
    Gillette account number: 725
  - Anderson, John R.- CCN 11 1943-1953 (Box 4, Folder 12)
    Gillette account number: 93
  - Andrews, James B.- CCN 12 1959-1960 (Box 4, Folder 13)
    Gillette account number: 2265
  - Archbell, J. E.- CCN 13 1941-1957 (Box 5, Folder 1)
    Gillette account number: 600
  - Arey, Dr.D. L.- CCN 14 1952-1963 (Box 5, Folder 2)
    Gillette account number: 1116
  - Aron, Bertha C.- CCN 15 1959-1962 (Box 5, Folder 3)
    Gillette account number: 2360
  - Askew, R. W.- CCN 16 1955-1960 (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Atlantic Beach Subdivision, - CCN 1085 n.d. (Box 5, Folder 5)
    Gillette account number: 2232
  - Atlantic Rural Exposition, - CCN 17 1946-1947 (Box 5, Folder 6)
    Gillette account number: 828
  - Automobile Club of America, - CCN 18 1950-1960 (Box 5, Folder 7)
    Gillette account number: 2261
  - Azalea Shopping Center, - CCN 19 1962-1964 (Box 5, Folder 8)
    Gillette account number: 2303
  - B General, 1941-1953 (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - B General, 1954-1968 (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - Baals, Donald D.- CCN 20 1955-1958 (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - Bahnsen, Henry- CCN 21 1943-1965 (Box 5, Folder 12)
    Gillette account number: 760
  - Baker, Mrs.Addison- CCN 22 1941-1954 (Box 6, Folder 1)
    Gillette account number: 831
  - Baptist Foreign Mission Board, - CCN 23 1958-1959 (Box 6, Folder 2)
    Gillette account number: 2221
  - Bard, Mrs.Ralph A.- CCN 24 1944-1954 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Barger,, Charles W.- CCN 25 1943-1945 (Box 6, Folder 4)
    Gillette account number: 750
  - Barium Springs, - CCN 26 1945-1948 (Box 6, Folder 5)
    Gillette account number: 845
  - Barnes, Carl Milton- CCN 27 1963-1968 (Box 6, Folder 6)
    Gillette account number: 2373
  - Barnes, H. Russ- CCN 29 1952-1953 (Box 6, Folder 7)
    Gillette account number: 1122
  - Barnes, Harold G.- CCN 28 1950-1951 (Box 6, Folder 8)
    Gillette account number: 1017
  - Barnett, Dr.T. Neil- CCN 30 1954-1968 (Box 6, Folder 9)
    Gillette account number: 2330
  - Barrus, Mrs.Alban K.- CCN 31 1947-1949 (Box 6, Folder 10)
    Gillette account number: 538
  - Barter Theater, - CCN 32 1948-1949 (Box 6, Folder 11)
    Gillette account number: 900
  - Bascom, Mrs.Joseph H.- CCN 33 1949-1951 (Box 6, Folder 12)
    Gillette account number: 969
  - Baskerville, Mrs.Henry M.- CCN 34 1945-1960 (Box 6, Folder 13)
    Gillette account number: 825
  - Battle, Hyman L.- CCN 35 1942-1945 (Box 7, Folder 1)
    Gillette account number: 609
  - Battle, Hyman L.- CCN 35 1946-1965 (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Battle, Thomas B.- CCN 36 1958-1963 (Box 7, Folder 3)
    Gillette account number: 2198
  - Bayliss, Maj.W. M. F.- CCN 37 1942-1968 (Box 7, Folder 4)
    Gillette account number: 726
  - Becker, Mrs.John V.- CCN 1225 1954 (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - Beirne, Miss Mary McD.- CCN 38 1942-1945 (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - Belk, Rev.J. Blanton- CCN 39 1948-1955 (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - Bell, Dr.Richard P.- CCN 40 1942-1957 (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - Bemiss, Samuel- CCN 41 1941-1968 (Box 7, Folder 9)
    Gillette account number: 716
  - Bennett, Mrs.Thomas R.- CCN 43 1958-1961 (Box 7, Folder 10)
    Gillette account number: 2216
  - Bennett College, - CCN 42 1938-1953 (Box 7, Folder 11)
    Gillette account number: 621
  - Benoit, Mrs.George- CCN 44 1946-1947 (Box 8, Folder 1)
    Gillette account number: 832
  - Benton Subdivision, - CCN 970 n.d. (Box 8, Folder 2)
    Gillette account number: 2019
  - Bethel Presbyterian Church, - CCN 45 1953-1954 (Box 8, Folder 3)
    Gillette account number: 1165
  - Binswanger, M. I.- CCN 46 1954-1958 (Box 8, Folder 4)
    Gillette account number: 2006
  - Bird, Mrs.F. G.- CCN 47 1942-1947 (Box 8, Folder 5)
    Gillette account number: 744
  - Birdsong Trust Fund, - CCN 48 1951 (Box 8, Folder 6)
    Gillette account number: 1058
  - Bizzell, Mrs.Edward- CCN 49 1946-1947 (Box 8, Folder 7)
    Gillette account number: 857
  - Blackstone College, - CCN 1007 n.d. (Box 8, Folder 8)
    Gillette account number: 2483
  - Blair, Donald M.- CCN 50 1942-1943 (Box 8, Folder 9)
    Gillette account number: 575
  - Blair, Louis- CCN 51 1964 (Box 8, Folder 10)
    Gillette account number: 3
  - Blakemore, Maj.M. N.- CCN 52 1942 (Box 8, Folder 11)
    Gillette account number: 708
  - Blanchard, Lawrence E.- CCN 53 1959-1962 (Box 8, Folder 12)
    Gillette account number: 2354
  - Blount, F. L.- CCN 54 1947 (Box 8, Folder 13)
    Gillette account number: 842
  - Blount, M. K.- CCN 55 1943-1945 (Box 8, Folder 14)
    Gillette account number: 755
  - Blount, M. K.- CCN 55 1946-1967 (Box 8, Folder 15)
  - Blow, George P.- CCN 170 1921 (Box 9, Folder 1)
    Gillette account number: 56
  - Blow, George P.- CCN 170 1922 Jan (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - Blow, George P.- CCN 170 1922 Feb (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - Blow, George P.- CCN 170 1922 Mar (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - Blow, George P.- CCN 170 1922 Apr-Jun (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - Blow, George P.- CCN 170 1922 Jly-Spt (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - Blow, George P.- CCN 170 1922 Oct-Dec (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - Blow, George P.- CCN 170 1923 Jan-Jun (Box 9, Folder 8)
  - Blow, George P.- CCN 170 1923 Jly-Dec (Box 9, Folder 9)
  - Blow, George P.- CCN 170 1924 Jan-Jun (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - Blow, George P.- CCN 170 1924 Jly-Dec (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - Blow, George P.- CCN 170 1925 (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - Blow, George P.- CCN 170 1926 (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - Blow, George P.- CCN 170 1927-1928 (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - Blow, George P.- CCN 170 n.d. (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - Blow, George W.- CCN 612 1942-1946 (Box 10, Folder 7)
    Gillette account number: 492
  - Blow, George W.- CCN 612 1947-1967 (Box 10, Folder 8)
  - Boisseau, Blair- CCN 56 1956-1965 (Box 11, Folder 1)
    Gillette account number: 2010
  - Bolling Square, - CCN 57 1945-1946 (Box 11, Folder 2)
    Gillette account number: 795
  - Bondurant, W. M.- CCN 58 1955-1959 (Box 11, Folder 3)
    Gillette account number: 2173
  - Bonynge, Mrs.Henry S.- CCN 1084 1944-1948 (Box 11, Folder 4)
    Gillette account number: 2151
  - Bonynge, Mrs.Henry A.- CCN 59 1959-1967 (Box 11, Folder 5)
    Gillette account number: 2153
  - Bounds, Mr.P. W.- CCN 1197 n.d. (Box 11, Folder 6)
    Gillette account number: 631
  - Bowen, Mrs.Harry- CCN 60 1953-1954 (Box 11, Folder 7)
    Gillette account number: 1161
  - Box, Mrs.George W- CCN 61 1957 (Box 11, Folder 8)
    Gillette account number: 2166
  - Boxley Farms Subdivision, - CCN 62 1956 (Box 11, Folder 9)
    Gillette account number: 2096
  - Boze, Edward S.- CCN 1100 1958-1959 (Box 11, Folder 10)
    Gillette account number: 2251
  - Brainard, Mrs. W. W., Jr.- CCN 64 1957-1964 (Box 11, Folder 11)
    Gillette account number: 2351
  - Branch, Patteson- CCN 66 1952 (Box 11, Folder 12)
  - Breeden, E. V.- CCN 65 1946-1947 (Box 11, Folder 13)
  - Bright, Mrs.Robert- CCN 67 1945-1946 (Box 11, Folder 14)
  - Brinkley, Dr.Arthur S., Jr.- CCN 68 1942-1965 (Box 11, Folder 15)
    Gillette account number: 670
  - Brinkley, Arthur S., Jr.- CCN 70 1955-1968 (Box 12, Folder 1)
    Gillette account number: 2220
  - Bristow, Robert A.- CCN 69 1966-1967 (Box 12, Folder 2)
    Gillette account number: 2484
  - Brown, Edwin P.- CCN 71 1952-1967 (Box 12, Folder 3)
    Gillette account number: 1113
  - Brown, J. Nelson- CCN 72 1953 (Box 12, Folder 4)
    Gillette account number: 1134
  - Brown, William M.- CCN 1129 1962-1963 (Box 12, Folder 5)
    Gillette account number: 2345
  - Bryan, Jonathan- CCN 74 1941 (Box 12, Folder 6)
    Gillette account number: 442
  - Bryan, Jonathan- CCN 74 1942-1944 (Box 12, Folder 7)
  - Bryan, Joseph, III- CCN 75 1962-1963 (Box 12, Folder 8)
  - Bryan, R. A.- CCN 76 1948-1949 (Box 12, Folder 9)
  - Bryan, Robert E.- CCN 77 1949 (Box 12, Folder 10)
    Gillette account number: 942
  - Bryan, Thomas P., Jr.- CCN 78 1966 (Box 12, Folder 11)
    Gillette account number: 2464
  - Desloge, Joseph- CCN 187 1945-1947 (Box 12, Folder 12)
    Gillette account number: 691
  - Buchanan, R. L., Jr.- CCN 79 n.d. (Box 12, Folder 12)
    Gillette account number: 2420
  - Bunn, J. P.- CCN 83 1949 (Box 12, Folder 13)
  - Burton, John G.- CCN 80 1947-1948 (Box 12, Folder 14)
    Gillette account number: 888
  - Butler, J. T.- CCN 81 1948-1949 (Box 12, Folder 15)
    Gillette account number: 882
  - Byrd, Mrs.Charles Wise- CCN 82 1956 (Box 12, Folder 16)
  - C General, 1942-1966 (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - Cabell, Mrs. Robert Gamble- CCN 84 1942 (Box 13, Folder 2)
    Gillette account number: 228
  - Cameron, Mrs.Bruce B.- CCN 85 1951 (Box 13, Folder 3)
    Gillette account number: 1041
  - Cameron, D. D.- CCN 86 1952-1953 (Box 13, Folder 4)
    Gillette account number: 1117
  - Camp, Hugh D. (Residence)- CCN 948 1952-1956 (Box 13, Folder 5)
    Gillette account number: 1044
  - Camp, Hugh D. (Subdivision)- CCN 87 1948 (Box 13, Folder 6)
    Gillette account number: 898
  - Camp, J. L., Jr.- CCN 88 1946-1953 (Box 13, Folder 7)
    Gillette account number: 812
  - Camp, J. L., Jr.- CCN 88 1954-1961 (Box 13, Folder 8)
  - Camp, John M., Jr.- CCN 90 1948-1961 (Box 13, Folder 9)
    Gillette account number: 881
  - Camp, J. L., III- CCN 89 1951-1961 (Box 13, Folder 9)
    Gillette account number: 496
  - Camp, Lawrence- CCN 91 1966 (Box 14, Folder 1)
  - Camp, Dr.Paul D.- CCN 92 1947-1967 (Box 14, Folder 2)
    Gillette account number: 833
  - Camp, R. J.- CCN 93 1955-1962 (Box 14, Folder 3)
    Gillette account number: 2113
  - Camp Subdivision, - CCN 94 1959-1963 (Box 14, Folder 4)
    Gillette account number: 2283
  - Candler, J. Boyer- CCN 1226 1944-1945 (Box 14, Folder 5)
    Gillette account number: 781
  - Cape Fear Valley Hospital, - CCN 95 1955-1957 (Box 14, Folder 6)
    Gillette account number: 2188
  - Capitol Square, - CCN 96 1954-1965 (Box 14, Folder 7)
    Gillette account number: 2207
  - Carlton, E. L.- CCN 97 1955-1960 (Box 14, Folder 8)
    Gillette account number: 2031
  - Carneal, J. D., Jr.- CCN 1093 n.d. (Box 14, Folder 9)
    Gillette account number: 1129
  - Carneal and Johnston, - CCN 1016 1958-1967 (Box 14, Folder 10)
    Gillette account number: 2222
  - Carson, R. J., Jr.- CCN 99 1958 (Box 14, Folder 11)
    Gillette account number: 2211
  - Carter, James- CCN 100 1962 (Box 14, Folder 12)
    Gillette account number: 2358
  - Carter, Robert Hill- CCN 101 1958 (Box 14, Folder 13)
    Gillette account number: 2201
  - Carter, Mrs.Spencer- CCN 102 1942-1950 (Box 14, Folder 14)
    Gillette account number: 688
  - Cauthorne, Ross- CCN 103 1943-1966 (Box 14, Folder 15)
    Gillette account number: 863
  - Cavalier Hotel, - CCN 104 1939-1946 (Box 14, Folder 16)
    Gillette account number: 231
  - Centenary Methodist Church, - CCN 105 1965-1966 (Box 14, Folder 17)
    Gillette account number: 2456
  - Central National Bank (Richmond, Va. - Patterson Avenue), - CCN 106 1968 (Box 15, Folder 1)
    Gillette account number: 2493
  - Central National Bank (Richmond, Va. - Thompson Street), - CCN 107 1956-1957 (Box 15, Folder 2)
    Gillette account number:
  - Central State Hospital, - CCN 108 1964-1965 (Box 15, Folder 3)
    Gillette account number: 2431
  - Central State Hospital, - CCN 108 1966-1967 (Box 15, Folder 4)
  - Cerebral Palsy Center, - CCN 109 1961-1965 (Box 15, Folder 5)
  - Chamberlin Hotel, - CCN 990 1948 (Box 15, Folder 6)
    Gillette account number: 299
  - Chase, Mrs.Clarence- CCN 110 1959-1963 (Box 15, Folder 7)
    Gillette account number: 2274
  - Chatham, H.- CCN 112 1951-1959 (Box 15, Folder 8)
    Gillette account number: 1024
  - Chatam Hall, - CCN 111 1944-1946 (Box 15, Folder 9)
    Gillette account number: 784
  - Cherry, Dr.Kenneth- CCN 113 1962-1965 (Box 15, Folder 10)
    Gillette account number: 2365
  - Chesapeake & Potomac Telephone Co., Christiansburg, VA, - CCN 114 1953-1954 (Box 16, Folder 1)
    Gillette account number: 1144
  - Chesapeake & Potomac Telephone Co., Danville, VA, - CCN 116 1957 (Box 16, Folder 2)
    Gillette account number: 2152
  - Chesapeake & Potomac Telephone Co., Leesburg, VA, - CCN 115 1955 (Box 16, Folder 3)
    Gillette account number: 2054
  - Chesapeake & Potomac Telephone Co., Lynchburg, VA, - CCN 117 1960 (Box 16, Folder 4)
    Gillette account number: 2298
  - Chesapeake & Potomac Telephone Co., Newport News, VA - Jefferson Avenue, - CCN 118 1958 (Box 16, Folder 5)
    Gillette account number: 2190
  - Chesapeake & Potomac Telephone Co., Newport News, VA - Warwick, - CCN 119 1953 (Box 16, Folder 6)
    Gillette account number: 1133
  - Chesapeake & Potomac Telephone Co., Norfolk, VA, - CCN 120 1957-1958 (Box 16, Folder 7)
    Gillette account number: 2155
  - Chesapeake & Potomac Telephone Co., Norfolk, VA - Sewells Point Road, - CCN 121 1950-1954 (Box 16, Folder 8)
    Gillette account number: 1010
  - Chesapeake & Potomac Telephone Co., Onancock, VA, - CCN 122 1956-1957 (Box 16, Folder 9)
    Gillette account number: 2066
  - Chesapeake & Potomac Telephone Co., Princess Anne Co., VA - Chinese Corner, - CCN 123 1957-1958 (Box 16, Folder 10)
    Gillette account number: 2154
  - Chesapeake & Potomac Telephone Co., Richmond, VA - Hermitage Road, - CCN 124 1957-1959 (Box 16, Folder 11)
    Gillette account number: 2120
  - Chesapeake & Potomac Telephone Co., Logan Street, - CCN 125 1959 (Box 16, Folder 12)
    Gillette account number: 2256
  - Chesapeake & Potomac Telephone Co., Richmond, VA, Nansemond Street, - CCN 126 1954-1958 (Box 16, Folder 13)
    Gillette account number: 1199
  - Chesapeake & Potomac Telephone Co., Richmond, VA - Patterson Avenue, - CCN 127 1950-1951 (Box 16, Folder 14)
    Gillette account number: 1005
  - Chesapeake & Potomac Telephone Co., Roanoke, VA, - CCN 128 1954-1958 (Box 16, Folder 15)
    Gillette account number: 2009
  - Chesapeake & Potomac Telephone Co., Toano, VA, - CCN 129 n.d. (Box 16, Folder 16)
    Gillette account number: 2146
  - Chesapeake & Potomac Telephone Co., Roanoke, VA - Cave Spring District, - CCN 977 n.d. (Box 16, Folder 17)
    Gillette account number: 2139
  - Chester Presbyterian Church, - CCN 130 n.d. (Box 17, Folder 1)
    Gillette account number: 2057
  - Chewning, Mrs.Carroll M.- CCN 131 1951-1961 (Box 17, Folder 2)
    Gillette account number: 2323
  - Chivers, J. H.- CCN 132 1951-1953 (Box 17, Folder 3)
    Gillette account number: 1062
  - Christ Church, Gordonsville, VA, - CCN 134 1945-1959 (Box 17, Folder 4)
    Gillette account number: 793
  - Christ Church, Greenville, SC, - CCN 135 1949-1950 (Box 17, Folder 5)
    Gillette account number: 982
  - Christian Children's Fund, Inc., - CCN 133 1965-1966 (Box 17, Folder 6)
    Gillette account number: 2434
  - Christian Children's Fund, Inc., - CCN 1147 n.d. (Box 17, Folder 7)
    Gillette account number: 2458
  - Chrystal Lake Estates, - CCN 1066 n.d. (Box 17, Folder 8)
    Gillette account number: 2062
  - Church of the Epiphany, - CCN 1060 n.d. (Box 17, Folder 9)
    Gillette account number: 2118
  - Clark, John W.- CCN 136 1957-1965 (Box 17, Folder 10)
    Gillette account number: 2158
  - Clarkson, J. Turner- CCN 137 1947-1950 (Box 17, Folder 11)
    Gillette account number: 879
  - Clarksville, Town of, - CCN 138 1950 (Box 17, Folder 12)
    Gillette account number: 996
  - Claytor House, - CCN 958 1936 (Box 17, Folder 13)
    Gillette account number: 555
  - Clintwood High School, - CCN 139 1955-1959 (Box 17, Folder 14)
    Gillette account number: 2045
  - Cochran, Mrs.Robert- CCN 140 1945-1948 (Box 18, Folder 1)
    Gillette account number: 816
  - Cocke, Dudley- CCN 141 1955 (Box 18, Folder 2)
  - Cohen, Leroy R., Jr.- CCN 142 1951-1954 (Box 18, Folder 3)
    Gillette account number: 1020
  - Cole, Dr.Dean B.- CCN 143 1945-1960 (Box 18, Folder 4)
    Gillette account number: 797
  - Cole Memorial Hospital, - CCN 144 1951 (Box 18, Folder 5)
  - Cole, Quincy- CCN 145 1950-1966 (Box 18, Folder 6)
    Gillette account number: 979
  - Cole, Quincy- CCN 145 1967-1968 (Box 18, Folder 7)
  - Colonial Williamsburg, - CCN 146 1952-1955 (Box 18, Folder 8)
  - Comer, M. C.- CCN 147 1945 (Box 18, Folder 9)
  - Commonwealth Club, - CCN 148 1967-1968 (Box 18, Folder 10)
    Gillette account number: 2463
  - Confederate Memorial Chapel, - CCN 1050 1961 (Box 18, Folder 11)
    Gillette account number: 2315
  - Connley, Spotswood- CCN 1028 n.d. (Box 18, Folder 12)
    Gillette account number: 2429
  - Connor, Mrs.H. G.- CCN 149 1949-1950 (Box 18, Folder 13)
  - Converse, Henry A.- CCN 150 1967-1968 (Box 18, Folder 14)
    Gillette account number: 2491
  - Cooke, Dorothy W.- CCN 151 1955 (Box 18, Folder 15)
    Gillette account number: 2081
  - Coonley, Mrs.Avery- CCN 152 1942-1950 (Box 18, Folder 16)
    Gillette account number: 70
  - Coonley, Mrs.Avery- CCN 152 1952-1959 (Box 18, Folder 17)
  - Cooper, Mrs.Dudley- CCN 153 1944-1946 (Box 19, Folder 1)
    Gillette account number: 769
  - Copeland, Mrs.Robert E.- CCN 1070 n.d. (Box 19, Folder 2)
    Gillette account number: 988
  - Corbitt, James H.- CCN 154 1944 (Box 19, Folder 3)
    Gillette account number: 36
  - Cornwell, E. W.- CCN 155 1951 (Box 19, Folder 4)
  - Country Club of Virginia, - CCN 1125 1951 (Box 19, Folder 5)
    Gillette account number: 171
  - Courtney, Lewis W.- CCN 156 1959 (Box 19, Folder 6)
    Gillette account number: 2266
  - Cozart, Mrs.S. M.- CCN 157 1951-1967 (Box 19, Folder 7)
    Gillette account number: 1072
  - Cozart, U. H.- CCN 1010 n.d. (Box 19, Folder 8)
    Gillette account number: 580
  - Cozart-Schaum Cemetery, - CCN 1073 1947 (Box 19, Folder 9)
    Gillette account number: 807
  - Craige, Mrs.Archibald- CCN 158 1963-1966 (Box 19, Folder 10)
    Gillette account number: 2401
  - Cranz, Dr.Oscar W.- CCN 159 1950-1957 (Box 19, Folder 11)
    Gillette account number: 1023
  - Craw, Mrs. Demas T.- CCN 160 1952 (Box 19, Folder 12)
  - Crestmede Subdivision, - CCN 1107 n.d. (Box 19, Folder 13)
    Gillette account number: 766
  - Cuchins, C. A., III- CCN 161 1948-1955 (Box 19, Folder 14)
    Gillette account number: 893
  - Cuchins, John A.- CCN 162 1967 (Box 19, Folder 15)
  - Culver, Mrs.B. M.- CCN 163 1949 (Box 19, Folder 16)
  - Cunningham, Misses Helen and Alice- CCN 164 1955-1967 (Box 19, Folder 17)
    Gillette account number: 2480
  - Cunningham, John R.- CCN 165 1957-1966 (Box 19, Folder 18)
    Gillette account number: 2076
  - Curlee, Shelby H.- CCN 949 1942-1965 (Box 19, Folder 19)
    Gillette account number: 720
  - Curlee, Shelby H. (Cemetery Plot)- CCN 949 1942 (Box 19, Folder 20)
  - Currie, John D.- CCN 167 1963-1966 (Box 19, Folder 21)
    Gillette account number: 2387
  - Currie, Robert A.- CCN 1227 1963-1964 (Box 19, Folder 22)
  - Cuykendall, Mrs.W. E.- CCN 168 1950-1951 (Box 19, Folder 23)
    Gillette account number: 1000
  - Cypress Cove Country Club, - CCN 169 1948 (Box 19, Folder 24)
    Gillette account number: 892
  - D General, 1942-1968 (Box 20, Folder 1)
  - Dan River Mills, - CCN 172 1951-1952 (Box 20, Folder 2)
  - Daniels, Frank A.- CCN 171 1946 (Box 20, Folder 3)
  - Danville Memorial Hospital, - CCN 173 1955-1956 (Box 20, Folder 4)
    Gillette account number: 2094
  - Danville Woman's Club, - CCN 174 1959 (Box 20, Folder 5)
    Gillette account number: 2276
  - Darling, Mrs.Kent- CCN 175 1955-1961 (Box 20, Folder 6)
    Gillette account number: 2090
  - Daughtridge, J. G.- CCN 176 1950 (Box 20, Folder 7)
    Gillette account number: 993
  - Davenport, Claude R.- CCN 177 1948-1965 (Box 20, Folder 8)
    Gillette account number: 850
  - Davenport, J. F. (Subdivision)- CCN 997 n.d. (Box 20, Folder 9)
    Gillette account number: 245
  - Davenport, Warwick B.- CCN 178 1958-1965 (Box 20, Folder 10)
  - Davidson College, - CCN 179 1942-1947 (Box 20, Folder 11)
    Gillette account number: 790
  - Davidson College, - CCN 179 1948-1950 (Box 20, Folder 12)
  - Davidson College, - CCN 179 1951-1954 (Box 20, Folder 13)
  - Davidson College, - CCN 179 1955-1958 (Box 21, Folder 1)
  - Davidson College, - CCN 179 1959-1961 (Box 21, Folder 2)
  - Davidson College, - CCN 179 1962-1968 (Box 21, Folder 3)
  - Davis, Mrs.G. Maslin- CCN 180 1953-1954 (Box 21, Folder 4)
    Gillette account number: 1163
  - Davis, J. Holmes, Sr.- CCN 181 1950-1955 (Box 21, Folder 5)
    Gillette account number: 1025
  - Davis, Dr.James E.- CCN 182 1956-1959 (Box 21, Folder 6)
    Gillette account number: 2104
  - DeColigny, Mrs.Calvert- CCN 183 1957-1962 (Box 21, Folder 7)
  - De Jarnette Sanitarium, - CCN 184 1967-1962 (Box 21, Folder 8)
  - Dent, Mrs.Magruder, Jr.- CCN 185 1957-1958 (Box 21, Folder 9)
    Gillette account number: 2183
  - Deopker, F. H.- CCN 1075 n.d. (Box 21, Folder 10)
    Gillette account number: 896
  - Depeyster, Mrs.Lucille- CCN 186 1941-1946 (Box 21, Folder 11)
  - Deuuy, Collins- CCN 188 n.d. (Box 21, Folder 13)
  - Devier, Maurice- CCN 189 1951 (Box 21, Folder 14)
  - Dickenson, Mrs.Alfred- CCN 191 1961 (Box 22, Folder 1)
    Gillette account number: 2314
  - Dickenson County Schools, - CCN 190 1953-1960 (Box 22, Folder 2)
  - Dickinson, Mrs.Hallowell- CCN 192 1956-1957 (Box 22, Folder 3)
    Gillette account number: 2080
  - Dillard, Mrs. Lester L.- CCN 193 1962 (Box 22, Folder 4)
    Gillette account number: 2363
  - Diocesan Memorial Episcopal Church, - CCN 194 1946-1947 (Box 22, Folder 5)
  - Dixie Hospital, - CCN 195 1958 (Box 22, Folder 6)
  - Dobbins, H. W.- CCN 196 1962-1963 (Box 22, Folder 7)
    Gillette account number: 2369
  - Dodson, Dr.Austin I.- CCN 197 1948-1949 (Box 22, Folder 8)
    Gillette account number: 891
  - Dominick, Mrs.H. W.- CCN 198 1963-1967 (Box 22, Folder 9)
    Gillette account number: 2367
  - Dortch, Hugh- CCN 199 1955 (Box 22, Folder 10)
  - Doyle, Wilber S.- CCN 200 1957-1959 (Box 22, Folder 11)
    Gillette account number: 2184
  - Drewry Mason High School, - CCN 611 1959 (Box 22, Folder 12)
    Gillette account number: 2267
  - Dudley, O. W.- CCN 201 1955-1965 (Box 22, Folder 13)
    Gillette account number: 2084
  - Duke, Charles J., Jr.- CCN 202 1947-1957 (Box 22, Folder 14)
    Gillette account number: 1088
  - Duke, Lee B.- CCN 203 1953 (Box 22, Folder 15)